<head>Deliverable 3<head>
<p>For my project I have decided to look into the sports that took place in 1905.
  So far in my newspaper articles I have only read about rugby football bein
  played in London between Wales and Scotland, but I am sure ther is more going
  on than just that throughout the entire year.  I want to figure out what they
  played, where they played it, how they organized it, and how competitive the
  games between teams were.  The answers to these questions can give us a huge
  insight into what their society was like and they can all be found within the
  text in this newspaper. You may be wondering how this will give us any insight
  into what it was like back then.  It will show us how the world functioned,
  what people care about, how they spend their free time, and how influential
  sports were then.  For example, our society today is very sports oriented.
  A lot of small talk and conversation starters are about football, basketball,
  hockey, soccer, and how certain teams are doing in their leagues.  The players
  on these big NFL, NBA, and NHL teams are treated like gods and get paid unreal
  amounts of money to perform out on the field.  People care very deeply and are
  extremely passionate about the team that they represent.  If I could find out
  what sports meant to these people back in 1905, we could figure out more of
  what it was like to live back then.  This information can also be used to find
  out how much income people made off of sports, the two correlate hand in hand.
  The other questions such as where they played it and how competitive it was are
  also very important.  If we find out where most of the games take place then
  we can consider that the so called sports capital of 1905.  We could find out
  that there is only one place where the games take place, or maybe there are a
  multitude of arenas where they switch off back and forth.  Whichever one it is,
  we will take the information that we get and learn from it.  Eventually we will
  have a much greater understanding of Alexandria in 1905, which is our overall
  goal in this class.<p>
